newsvoting.com 2015-04-10

# Privacy Policy | NewsVoting

## News Voting Privacy Policy Overview

This Privacy Policy covers News Voting's treatment of personal information that is recorded when you register for membership and submit comments and/or news content for inclusion in our database. 

Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on the News Voting web site, nor does it extend to people that News Voting does not employ or manage. 

## Information Collection and Use

Anyone can visit News Voting and browse the news content and comments without having to provide personal information. We do, however, gather information from individuals who wish to submit news, ratings and comments. This information is collected both directly and through the use of "cookies". 

Direct collection of information is limited to the details requested of you at the time of registration such as your email address, gender, date of birth, location and a password. 

You may remove yourself from any or all of our notice and announcement mailings at anytime using the unsubscribe methods provided in those mailings. Any mailing received from our company is clearly identified and includes a valid email address and unsubscribe link which you can use to remove yourself from future mailings. Should you encounter problems in this regard, contact removemylinkfast[at]gmail.com. Our turnaround time for responding to unsubscribe requests is generally 24 hours. 

The other way we collect information is through the use of cookies. When you register with News Voting, a "cookie" may be placed on your computer. Cookies are bits of information that a web site places on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping and activity-tracking purposes. Cookies cannot be used to learn your identity unless you have previously provided that information to that web site or your web browser automatically provides that information. 

In conjunction with the registration information you provide, cookies help us recognize you when you return to the site, and they let you avoid having to log-in each time you visit. Moreover, cookies may be helpful in helping us determine the direction of future upgrades and enable us to better personalize our service to match your interests. 

The only other information collected is the data recorded on our server log files. Typically this information includes IP address, browser type, domain name, referral URL, country of origin, pages visited, entry points, and exit points, but this data is NOT correlated in any fashion to personally identifying information. 

## Advertising Cookies

Ad networks and third party vendors, including Google, may place cookies on your browser while visiting News Voting. Google's DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads based on your visit to News Voting and/or other websites. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie here and cookies from many other ad networks here. 

## Protecting Your Privacy on News Voting

As a registered user you are able to not just submit and rate news, you are also able to post comments. Please be aware that your posted comments are publicly accessible. Caution should be exercised in disclosing any personal details. Although it is not uncommon for email addresses to be included in comment posts, it is not required. The same is true of any personal information. 

## Security

Any information you provide, other than information you chose to provide and make publicly available in your posts, is maintained and accessible only by News Voting staff, and only by those of our staff with a need to have access to such information in the performance of their duties. News Voting has implemented commercially reasonable security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control or in our possession. 

Notwithstanding the above, we do not and cannot warrant the security of the information that you provide. Accordingly, you agree that you are providing such information at your own risk. 

## Special Cases

News Voting's policy is not to use or share personal information about visitors or members in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. Notwithstanding anything in this policy to the contrary, News Voting may, however, disclose personal information about visitors or members, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms and Conditions or other user policies; to operate the Services properly; or to protect newsvoting.com and our Members. 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

News Voting may amend this policy from time to time. If significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, you will be notified by email or a prominent announcement will be posted on our site notifying you of the change. 

## Questions or Comments

Questions or comments may be sent to: bookmarkingwebmaster[at]gmail.com

## Acceptance of Terms

By using this site you acknowledge and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as outlined above. If you disagree with any term or condition in this Privacy Policy, you must not use our site.
